Jacob Cadiente

Full Stack Developer

646 Whittingham Place Lake Mary, FL 321-662-9165 jacob.cadiente@gmail.com

SKILLS

Heavy first hand experience with languages such as PHP, SQL, HTML5, CSS, Sass/SCSS and Javascript, including Javascript frameworks such as Node.js, React.js, Vue.js. Knowledgeable in dev tools such as ORM's, IDE's, Vagrant/Ubuntu, Jira, Scrum and Git.

I bring hard work, dedication and a passion for OOP and UI/UX. I thrive in team environments and love bouncing ideas and creativity off one another

EXPERIENCE

GoPort, Orlando - Full Stack Developer

April 2019 - PRESENT

- Coded entire features/pages front to back using PHP, JS, SQL.
- Over saw a complete front end rework into a new Design System.
- Managed a SQL database of over 140 tables.

Push Inc, Orlando - Front End Developer/Freelance

Jan 2019 - April 2019

- Front end dev using Wordpress, Node, React, Vue and PHP.
- Assisted on many portfolios including Sonny's BBQ, Teleties, Yardhouse.

Gratsee, Orlando - Associate Developer

Oct. 2018 - Dec. 2018

- Learned/assisted in mobile development using React Mobile, Java.
- Worked in a highly efficient SCRUM workflow.

EDUCATION

UCF Coding Bootcamp, Orlando - Web Development Certification

MARCH 2018 - OCT. 2018